Arthur J. Pulos Papers
Arthur J. Pulos Papers
1958-1983
Pulos, Arthur J.
approx. 248 linear ft.
Papers of the American industrial designer; professor, Syracuse University. Office records for Pulos Design Associates, Inc., including correspondence, drawings, photographs and slides for jobs for various clients.
149398
Biographical History
Arthur Jon Pulos (1917-1997) was an American industrial designer. He earned his undergraduate degree in art education from Carnegie Institute of Technology (now Carnegie-Mellon University) in 1939 and a Master of Fine Arts (MFA) in silversmithing from the University of Oregon in 1943. He was an Army Air Corps veteran of World War II, founder and president of Pulos Design Associates (1958-1988), and professor of industrial design at Syracuse University (1955-1982). He also served as consultant and lecturer in more than 25 countries; in 1985 he was the United States delegate to the Budapest Cultural Forum, and he lectured at the Beijing Academy of Art and Design in China in 1987.
Pulos received numerous awards over his career, including honors for silver design at the 1958 World's Fair, the first Design Education Award (Industrial Designers Society of America, 1988), the Premio Mexico (1996), and Japan's Seventh International Design Award (Osaka, 1995). He was an honorary fellow of the Design Institute of Australia and of the Mexican Academy of Design, and was named to the policy panel of the Design Arts Program for the National Endowment for the Arts. His work is in the permanent collections of museums across the United States.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Arthur J. Pulos Papers consists of Design practice/office records, Personal records, and Business records.
Pulos Design Associates' Design practice/office records form the bulk of the collection and includes correspondence, photographs, slides, and drawings for a number of corporate clients of Pulos' company, some local to Central New York and others nationally established. Among the corporations represented are Baldwin Technology, Camillus Cutlery, Crouse-Hinds, Dictaphone, Empire Airlines, Gaylord Brothers, General Electric, Pass & Seymour, Piper Aircraft, Rockwell International, Ridge Tool Company, Satellite Business Systems, Swingline, Syracuse China, Syracuse University, and Welch Allyn. Records are ordered alphabetically by client and job numbers (a two-letter code with sequential numbers) are provided -- for example "AB-1" through "AB-7" for Abbot. Files which include photographs, slides and/or drawings (separately boxed) are so indicated.
Personal records cover nearly thirty years, while Business records includes Pulos' business certificate, empoyee work agreements, and personal time records and calendars.
At the end of the collection is a box listing of the 2000 accession, which has had only minimal processing. This accession contains more than 60 boxes of material from Arthur J. Pulos and from Pulos Design Associates, including correspondence, office records, sketches, photographs, slides, notes, drafts of book chapters, research material, and much more.
Arrangement of the Collection
Design practice/office records are arranged alphabetically by client name, followed by non-client projects and some miscellaneous items. Drawings, housed separately in flat files, are referenced by number.
The 2000 accession has not been processed and remains in original order. Note that this accession has a separate box-numbering sequence, beginning again with Box 1. When requesting a box by number, please specify whether it is part of the 2000 accession.
Related Material
Professor Pulos' records relating to his tenure at Syracuse University are held by the University Archives.
Subject and Genre Headings
Industrial Design; Pulos, Arthur J.; Pulos Design Associates.; Design, Industrial -- United States.; Industrial designers -- United States.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Drawings (visual works); Photographs.; Slides (photographs); Scrapbooks.; Industrial designers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Arthur J. Pulos.
Inventory
- Design practice/office records
  - Abbott
    - AB-1 Consort, 1983; includes slides (Box 1)
    - AB-2 Exacta, 1983 (Box 1)
    - AB-3 IMP, 1983 (Box 1)
    - AB-4 Currency scale, 1983 (Box 1)
    - AB-5 Coin counter, 1983 (Box 1)
    - AB-6 Small IMP, 1983 (Box 1)
    - AB-7 Oizumi coin counter, 1983; includes slides (Box 1)
  - Adirondack (Box 1)
  - Aeolian American (Box 1)
  - Albany International
    - AL-1 Pool table, 1974 (Box 1)
    - AL-2 Children's bicycle seat, 1975 (Box 1)
  - ARMCO Steel (Box 1)
  - Baldwin Technology Corporation
    - BA-1Gen corporate identity program, 1982; includes photographs, slides (Box 1)
    - BA-2SG 260 Automix, 1982; includes slides (Box 1)
    - BA-3CK Control panel, 1981 (Box 1)
    - BA-4A Stacker/bundler, 1981; includes slides (Box 1)
    - BA-5CG H.S. Sheeter bridge, 1980; includes slides (Box 1)
    - BA-6SG 20 Gal. Flexo-ink circulator, 1982 (Box 1)
    - BA-7SG 333 Ink level controller, 1982-83 (Box 1)
    - BA-8SG 660 Circulating water level, 1982 (Box 1)
    - BA-9SG In-line automix, 1982 (Box 1)
    - BA-10SG 831 Frigid-flo labels, 1982 (Box 1)
    - BA-11SG Microset glue softener, 1982 (Box 1)
    - BA-12SG Auto. blanket cleaner, 1982 (Box 1)
    - BA-13SG Aquamarine Ph control, 1983 (Box 1)
    - BA-14WC Microtrol, 1983; includes slides (Box 1)
    - BA-15SG 452 Intermittent gluer, 1983 (Box 1)
    - BA-16M Product nameplates, 1983 (Box 1)
    - BA-17SG 270 Automix artwork, 1983-84 (Box 1)
  - Becton-Dickinson
    - BD-1 Disposable Thermometer, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Bennett-Ireland
    - BE-1 Fire screen, 1963 (Box 1)
    - BE-2 Andirons, 1964 (Box 1)
    - BE-3 Packaging, 1964; includes photographs (Box 1)
    - BE-4 Grilladier, 1964; includes photographs, slides (Box 1)
    - BE-5 Wrought iron tools, 1964 (Box 1)
    - BE-6 Firelighter package, 1964-65 (Box 1)
    - BE-7 Flextong box, 1964-65 (Box 1)
    - BE-8 Tinder brix, 1965 (Box 1)
    - BE-9 Stowable log carrier, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Blount-Parker
    - BA-1 Cherub bath, 1963 (Box 1)
    - BA-2 Bath, 1963 (Box 1)
    - BA-3 Play yard, 1963 (Box 1)
    - BA-4 Chiffonette, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Camillus Cutlery
    - CC-1 Kitchen tools, 1956; includes photographs (Box 1)
  - Cazenovia Ski Club
    - CA-1 Fireplace, 1961; includes slides (Box 1)
    - CA-2 Badge, 1961; includes photographs (Box 1)
  - Combustion Equipment Associates
    - CEA-1 Corporate identity program, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Coyne Industrial Laundries
    - CO-1 Airport display graphics, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Crouse-Hinds
    - CR-1 Flood light, 1961 (Box 1)
    - CR-2 12" Traffic signal redesign, 1961; includes slides (Box 1)
  - Dictaphone Corporation
    - Dictaphone billings, slides, photos, 1972-82 (Box 2)
    - DC-1 24l Cassette, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-2 Underwater detector, 1973; includes slides (Box 3)
    - DC-3 Recorder, 1973; includes photographs, slides (Box 3)
    - DC-4 Logger, 1972-73; includes slides (Box 3)
    - DC-5 Ansafone, 1972-76 (Box 3)
    - DC-6 Pot. communication systems, 1972-75; includes slides (Box 3)
    - DC-7 Model 191 hand microphone, 1972-73 (Box 3)
    - DC-8 Interior, 1972-73 (Box 3)
    - DC-9 Packaging, 1972-73 (Box 3)
    - DC-10 Trademark label, 1972-73 (Box 3)
    - DC-11 Color standards program, 1972-73 (Box 3)
    - DC-12 Multi media device artwork, 1972-73 (Box 3)
    - DC-13 193 Thought tank system, 1973-74; includes photographs, slides (Box 3)
    - DC-14 Thought tank trademark label, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-15 Courtroom recorder, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-16 Thought tank name label, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-17 Face plate - transcribe station, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-18 Face plate - dictate station, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-19 Model 191 name & rating plate, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-20 Call diverter, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-21 Transcribe station, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-22 500 Dictation machine, 1973-75; includes slides (Box 3)
    - DC-23 Product graphics manual, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-24 Order taker, 1973-74; includes slides (Box 3)
    - DC-25 Interior/bridgeport color study, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-26 Message repeater, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-27 Dicta 10 mini, 1973-75; includes photographs (Box 3)
    - DC-28 Voltage detector, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-30 Ansafone 640, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-31 Tool kit, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-32 Connector block, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-33 Ansacall, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-34 Advance hand set, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-35 Corporate graphics manual, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-36 Comb. gas detector, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-37 Pipe locator, 1973-74 (Box 3)
    - DC-38 Bridgeport exterior, 1973 (Box 3)
    - DC-39 Portable cassette, 1974-75 (Box 3)
    - DC-40 242 Desk cassette, 1974-77; includes photographs, slides (Box 3)
    - DC-41 Fixed gas detector, 1974 (Box 3)
    - DC-42 DC-10 Cover colors, 1974 (Box 3)
    - DC-43 Low cost 242, 1974 (Box 3)
    - DC-44 4000 Logger Mark II, 1974 (Box 3)
    - DC-45 Ansafone colors and graphics, 1974-76 (Box 3)
    - DC-46 Magnetic tape package, 1974 (Box 3)
    - DC-47 Mini-foot switch, 1974 (Box 3)
    - DC-48 Order taker unit, 1974-75 (Box 3)
    - DC-49 Model 220 Cassette recorder, 1975-78 (Box 3)
    - DC-50 192 Thought tank, 1975-76; includes slides (Box 3)
    - DC-51 Stacked cassette recorder, 1975-77 (Box 4)
    - DC-52 Model 210 color and graphics, 1975-76 (Box 4)
    - DC-53 Lifeguard, 1975-76; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-54 Packaging program, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-55 DC-1 Mini cassette, 1976 (Box 4)
    - DC-56 Mini-cassette adapter, 1976; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-57 Model 120 cassette recorder, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-58 MCL logger, 1976; includes photographs, slides (Box 4)
    - DC-59 Long range program, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-60 Micro-cassette (model 130), 1977-1978; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-61 Desk models DC-4 and DC-5, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-62 Redo model 10, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-63 Thought master international plate, 1976-77 (Box 4)
    - DC-64 Model 11 redesign, 1976-77 (Box 4)
    - DC-65 Model 130 for Copal, Japan, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-66 Model 696 graphics, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-67 Hands free microphone, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-68 New mini-cassette, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-69 Thought master - new colors, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-70 Hebb presentation, 1977-78 (Box 4)
    - DC-71 640/690 Ansafone face lift, 1977; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-72 Micro-cassette label, 1977-78 (Box 4)
    - DC-73 Thought Master II, 1977-78 (Box 4)
    - DC-74 Dictacall, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-75 Micro adapter, 1977-78 (Box 4)
    - DC-76 Touch tone encoder, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-77 Brazos, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-78 Central status system, 1978-79 (Box 4)
    - DC-79 Panasonic sketches, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-80 Small work group, 1977 (Box 4)
    - DC-81 DCX, 1979-81; includes photographs, slides (Box 4)
    - DC-82 JVC portable, 1977-79; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-83 New 220, 1977-79 (Box 4)
    - DC-84 Thought Master 225, 1977-78 (Box 4)
    - DC-85 Micro Cassette Portable 325, 1978 (Box 4)
    - DC-86 290 recorder, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-87 Dictation logging system, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-88 Ansafone graphics, 1978-80 (Box 4)
    - DC-89 Ansafone X, 1978-80 (Box 4)
    - DC-90 Mastermind graphics, 1978-80 (Box 4)
    - DC-91 Mini Cassette 250 graphics, 1978 (Box 4)
    - DC-92 Micro cassette graphics, 1978 (Box 4)
    - DC-93 4000 Logger (renamed 5000), 1978-81; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-94 CSD terminals, 1978 (Box 4)
    - DC-95 193 Mini console, 1978-79 (Box 4)
    - DC-96 325 Micro portable, 1979-80; includes slides (Box 4)
    - DC-97 Model 225 portable, 1979-80 (Box 4)
    - DC-98 Scully table top console, 1979 (Box 4)
    - DC-99 Long range presentation, 1979-80 (Box 4)
    - DC-100 Model 2251 standard portable, 1979-81 (Box 4)
    - DC-101 Low cost transcriber, 1979 (Box 4)
    - DC-102 Pitney-bowes corporate I.D., 1979-80 (Box 5)
    - DC-103 Future control systems, 1979-80 (Box 5)
    - DC-104 Transcribing station study, 1979-80 (Box 5)
    - DC-105 PPX Ultra-thin portable, 1979-82; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-106 Dual media transcribe station, 1979-80; includes photographs (Box 5)
    - DC-107 Model 125/2 face lift, 1979-80; includes photographs (Box 5)
    - DC-108 Model 124/0 economy version, 1979-81; includes photographs (Box 5)
    - DC-109 Model 125/3, 1979-81 (Box 5)
    - DC-110 Integrated office system, 1979; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-111 Patent labels, 1979-80 (Box 5)
    - DC-112 Medical package, 1979-80 (Box 5)
    - DC-113 Revised dictation station, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-114 3M Cassette logger, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-115 Dictation systems presentation, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-116 Thought tank covers, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-117 Cassette eraser package, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-118 Corporate display, 1980-81 (Box 5)
    - DC-119 Star portable, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-120 Ansafone X redesign, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-121 Broadcast Logger, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-122 Artec display terminal, 1980; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-123 Model 293 SCR program, 1980 (Box 5)
    - DC-124 Ansafone 640 redesign, 1980-81 (Box 5)
    - DC-125 Artec packaging program, 1980-81 (Box 5)
    - DC-126 Model 225/1 Pamco portable, 1980-81 (Box 5)
    - DC-127 NDS terminal, 1980-81 (Box 5)
    - DC-128 CDS console, 1981-82 (Box 5)
    - DC-129 CDS master mind, 1981-82 (Box 5)
    - DC-130 Microcassette changer, 1981 (Box 5)
    - DC-131 Microcassette changer (CDS), 1981-82; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-132 CDS Standard cassette changer, 1981-82 (Box 5)
    - DC-133 Software accessories, 1981-82 (Box 5)
    - DC-134 Dual cassette ansafone, 1981 (Box 5)
    - DC-135 PDX Desktop transcriber, 1981-82; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-136 JVC 3240, 1981-82; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-137 3350 Economy micro transcriber, 1982; includes photographs (Box 5)
    - DC-138 NDS Computer paint and graphics, 1982 (Box 5)
    - DC-139 JVC Recharger pack, 1982 (Box 5)
    - DC-140 727 Ansafone revision, 1982 (Box 5)
    - DC-141 2250 MkII stereo, 1982 (Box 5)
    - DC-142 Long range presentation, 1982; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DC-143 Cassette label artwork, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Diemolding Corporation
    - DM-2 Snack tray, 1967; includes photographs (Box 5)
    - DM-3 Consulting services, 1967 (Box 5)
    - DM-4 Cheese spreader, 1968 (Box 5)
    - DM-5 Maxim carafe, 1969; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DM-6 Electra-perk, 1969; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DM-7 Range top percolator, 1969; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DM-8 Closure for maxim jar, 1969; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DM-9 Sonac denture cleaner, 1970; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DM-10 Aqua-fem, 1972 (Box 5)
    - DM-11 Skin massager, 1972 (Box 5)
    - DM-12 Tooth polisher, 1973 (Box 5)
  - R. E. Dietz Corporation
    - DI-1 Lead light/hazard warning, 1958; includes photographs, slides (Box 5)
    - DI-2 Electric search light, 1958; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DI-3 Combination rear view/spotlight, 1958-59; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DI-4 Barricade system, 1959; includes slides (Box 5)
    - DI-5 Turn signals, 1959; includes photographs (Box 5)
  - Disston Corporation
    - DS-1 Flexible cord grass trimmer, 1976; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-2 Cordless stapler (Box 6)
    - DS-3 Saw handles, 1976-77 (Box 6)
    - DS-4 Long range program, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-5 Soldering gun, 1976; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-6 Outdoor color and graphics program, 1976-77; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-7 Glue gun, 1977 (Box 6)
    - DS-8 Scrubber, 1977; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-9 Hand guard, 1976-77 (Box 6)
    - DS-10 Abrader, 1977; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-11 Nest saw, 1976; includes slides (Box 6)
    - DS-12 Low cost pump sprayer, 1976 (Box 6)
    - DS-13 Power pack pruner, 1976 (Box 6)
    - DS-14 Power pack camplight, 1976-77 (Box 6)
    - DS-15 Power pack carving knife, 1976 (Box 6)
    - DS-16 Pistol grip screwdriver/drill, 1976-77 (Box 6)
    - DS-17 Folding work bench, 1976-77 (Box 6)
    - DS-18 European power pack, 1977 (Box 6)
    - DS-19 Hacksaw line, 1977 (Box 6)
    - DS-20 Yard trimmer, 1977 (Box 6)
    - DS-21 Wood handle saw line, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Electric Furnace Company
    - EF-1 Corporate identity program, 1983 (Box 6)
    - EF-2 Long range program, 1983 (Box 6)
    - EF-3 Luber, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Emerson Electric Company, 1978 (Box 6)
  - EMESCO, 1963-64 (Box 6)
  - Emhart Corporation
    - EM-1 Feeder arm, 1984 (Box 6)
    - EM-1A Pressure/temperature control panel, 1984 (Box 6)
    - EM-2 Electronics & control panel graphics, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Empire Airlines
    - EA-1 "Metro" exterior paint, 1977; includes slides (Box 6)
    - EA-2 "Chieftain" exterior paint, 1977 (Box 6)
    - EA-3 Airlines logotype, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Erie Canal
    - ER-1 Graphics program, 1970-74; includes photographs, slides (Box 6)
  - Frazier Company
    - FR-1 Flatware, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Gaylord Brothers
    - GA-1 Book charging system, 1961; includes photographs (Box 6)
    - GA-2 Card holder, 1961; includes photographs (Box 6)
  - General Binding Corporation
    - GB-1 455 Binder, 1984; includes slides (Box 6)
    - GB-2 Vello-bind, 1984; includes slides (Box 6)
  - General Electric Corporation
    - GE-1 Genographic, 1960 (Box 6)
    - GE-2 Clock/radio, 1960 (Box 6)
    - GE-3 Toy, 1962 (Box 6)
    - GE-4 Concepts for audio products, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Gibson International
    - GF-1 Dinette group, 1972 (Box 6)
    - GF-2 16-20 Chrome and leather chair, 1972; includes photographs, slides (Box 6)
    - GF-3 Wood & leather dinette group, 1962; includes slides (Box 6)
    - GF-4 Upholstered leather group (Box 6)
  - Graco, Incorporated
    - GR-1 Cup gun, 1983 (Box 6)
    - GR-2 Semi-pro airless sprayer, 1983; includes slides (Box 6)
  - Impact Business Machines, 1968-69 (Box 6)
  - John Thomas
    - JT-1 Deck setter, 1981 (Box 6)
    - JT-2 Safemate graphics, 1981; includes slides (Box 6)
    - JT-3 Screw locator, 1981 (Box 6)
    - JT-4 Desktop staplers, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Kent Company
    - KE-1 Commercial vacuum cleaner, 1958; includes slides (Box 6)
    - KE-2 Turbo vac model 55, 1959 (Box 6)
    - KE-3 Comet line of vacuums, 1960-61; includes photographs (Box 6)
  - Link Aviation Company, 1959 (Box 7)
  - McIntosh Company
    - MC-1 Stereo fronts (Box 7)
  - Microanalog Associates
    - MA-1 Graphics program, 1983; includes photographs (Box 7)
  - Mohawk Industries
    - MO-1 PBR System, corporate identity, 1969-71; includes slides (Box 7)
  - National Special Media Institute
    - NS-1 IDI System analysis, 1971 (Box 7)
    - NS-2 IDI System prototype development, 1971 (Box 7)
    - NS-3 Game board development, 1971 (Box 7)
    - NS-4 IDI System assembly, 1971 (Box 7)
    - NS-5 IDI Graphics program, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Nautalloy Products
    - NA-1 Steering wheel horn rim, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Onondaga Community College
    - OCC-1 Campus graphics program, 1971; includes slides (Box 7)
  - Pass & Seymour, Incorporated
    - PA-Gen General consulting services, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-1 Wall lamps, 1963; includes photographs (Box 7)
    - PA-2 Switchplate, 1963 (Box 7)
    - PA-4 Receptacle (Box 7)
    - PA-5 Dimmer switch (Box 7)
    - PA-7 General fixture consulting, 1965 (Box 7)
    - PA-8 New product research program, 1964 (Box 7)
    - PA-10 3 Plug receptacle face, 1964 (Box 7)
    - PA-11 Ceiling fixture, 1964 (Box 7)
    - PA-12 New product research, 1965 (Box 7)
    - PA-13 Decorator textures, 1965 (Box 7)
    - PA-14 Custom products, 1965-66 (Box 7)
    - PA-15 Ceiling fixture, 1965-66 (Box 7)
    - PA-16 3 Receptacle grounding outlet, 1966 (Box 7)
    - PA-17 Entrance, 1971; includes photographs (Box 7)
    - PA-18 Reception area, 1972-76 (Box 7)
    - PA-19 Exterior plant scheme (Box 7)
    - PA-22 Face treatment heavy duty outlet (Box 7)
    - PA-23 Plant interior program, 1975-78 (Box 7)
    - PA-24 Signage system, 1973; includes slides (Box 7)
    - PA-G1 Ground fault interrupter outlet, 1972-73; includes photographs (Box 7)
    - PA-G2 Hospital wiring devices, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G3 Rocker switch plate, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G4 20 Amp connector, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G5 Product line appearance, 1972-74 (Box 7)
    - PA-G6 Square opening devices, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G7 Turnlok device color coding, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G8 Motor base outlet, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G9 20 Amp GFI outlet, 1972 (Box 7)
    - PA-G10 Right angle connector, 1973 (Box 7)
    - PA-G11 50 Amp right angle connector, 1973 (Box 7)
    - PA-G12 Heavy duty switch, 1973 (Box 7)
    - PA-G13 GFI wall plate, 1973 (Box 7)
    - PA-G14 Portable GFI, 1973 (Box 7)
    - PA-G16 50 Amp outlet, 1974 (Box 7)
    - PA-G17 Designer line outlets, 1974 (Box 7)
    - PA-G18 Weatherproof power inlet, 1974 (Box 7)
    - PA-G20 Designer line switchplates, 1974 (Box 7)
    - PA-G21 Revised GFI outlet, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Piper Aircraft Corporation
    - PI-Gen General consulting, 1972-75; includes photographs, slides (Box 8)
    - PI-1 Design program for 1974 aircraft, 1972-76; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-2 Graphics manual, 1972-73; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-3 Pressurized Navajo, 1972-73; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-4 Arapaho, 1973; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-5 Chieftain Navajo, 1972-74 (Box 8)
    - PI-6 Lakeland plant development, 1973 (Box 8)
    - PI-7 Pressurized Aztec, 1972-74 (Box 8)
    - PI-8 Single Engine Comanche, 1973 (Box 8)
    - PI-9 Navajo interior, 1973-75 (Box 8)
    - PI-10 325 Navajo, 1973 (Box 8)
    - PI-11 Turbo Navajo, 1973 (Box 8)
    - PI-12 PA-23 Aztec, 1973-75; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-13 Service employee uniforms, 1973 (Box 8)
    - PI-14 Trainer, 1973 (Box 8)
    - PI-15 Design program 1975 aircraft, 1973-74; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-16 Vero Beach Aircraft-1976 program, 1974-75; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-17 Interior development, 1974-75 (Box 8)
    - PI-18 Long Range Prog. Navajo Interiors, 1974-75 (Box 8)
    - PI-19 Vero Beach interior development, 1974-75 (Box 8)
    - PI-20 Customer selection center, 1974-75 (Box 8)
    - PI-21 Cabin class interior program, 1973-75; includes photographs, slides (Box 8)
    - PI-22 Long range exterior color program, 1973-75; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-23 Vero Beach interiors program, 1975-76; includes photographs (Box 8)
    - PI-24 1977 Program, 1975-76; includes photographs (Box 8)
    - PI-25 PA42 and PA43 interiors, 1975-76; includes photographs (Box 8)
    - PI-26 1978 Program, 1975-77; includes photographs, slides (Box 8)
    - PI-27 Corpac interior display panels, 1975 (Box 8)
    - PI-28 Chieftain interiors program, 1976-77; includes photographs, slides (Box 8)
    - PI-29 Custom color scheme, 1976; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-30 Cub exterior paint scheme, 1976 (Box 8)
    - PI-31 Long range interiors program, 1976 (Box 8)
    - PI-32 Pawnee exterior, 1976; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-33 Arrow III exterior scheme, 1976 (Box 8)
    - PI-34 1978 Vero Beach optional interiors, 1976-77; includes photographs, slides (Box 8)
    - PI-35 1978 Navajo optional interiors, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-36 "T" Tail aircraft, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-37 1979 Exterior program, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-38 1979 Vero Beach interiors, 1977-78 (Box 8)
    - PI-39 1979 Aztec "F" interiors, 1977 (Box 8)
    - PI-40 1979 Exterior ident. graphics, 1977-78 (Box 8)